(Sheldon:)the phone companies
have been lying to me.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
Penny. Penny.
(Penny:)You do realize I stand
on the other side of the door
(Penny:)waiting for you to finish
knocking three times.
(Sheldon:)I know. I can see the shadow
of your feet under the door.
(Penny:)Yeah, my point is
it's a waste of time.
(Sheldon:)If you're looking for an example
(Sheldon:)of a waste of time,
I would refer you
(Sheldon:)to the conversation
we're having right now.
(Penny:)What do you want?
(Sheldon:)I've decided to take your advice
and have arranged
(Sheldon:)to go on a date
with Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Penny:)Oh, that's great.
(Penny:)Have fun.
Wait.
(Sheldon:)You have to drive me.
(Penny:)What?
You know I don't drive.
(Penny:)Well, go ask Leonard.
I did.
(Sheldon:)He said-- and I quote--
"Ask Penny.
It was her cockamamy idea."
Leonard said "cockamamy"?
(Sheldon:)Actually, I'm paraphrasing.
(Sheldon:)Having been raised
in a Christian household,
(Sheldon:)I'm uncomfortable
with the language he used.
(Sheldon:)And to be honest,
(Sheldon:)I'm not entirely comfortable
with "cockamamy."